Something that I'm disturbed by as we woke up this morning is seeing folks on the Internet say that this was a false flag, that we are basically all in cahoots to say that this was staged.
And I think as someone who, for all of us, who was in the room, who had to jump on the ground, who had to text our family and friends and tell them that we're OK, calling our moms, like so many people in this country have done.
For decades, to see people say those kinds of things, it is frustrating and it's disturbing.
It shows the issues that we have to try and fix.
I ain't never seen this brand of coon in my life. He's sitting up there on basically state-sponsored television, rocking a natural.
Let's break it down. His feelings were hurt by people calling a hoax a hoax.
Sir, you are not sitting here comparing your experience at the White House Correspondence Center with that of children dealing with active shooters in schools.
With people who are present at the Pulse nightclub in Orlando, Florida.
You can't. Nah, you can't possibly be doing that because that would be insane.
First of all, why are you at the White House Correspondence Center?
Oh, because you're on mainstream media and you're complicit in the advancement of the disinformation and misinformation and propaganda campaigns that are harming the citizens of the United States and the world on a daily basis.
But you have tricked yourself into thinking because you're in your position that it's somehow more ethical and more moral or better because it's you, right?
Because I haven't seen you calling attention to the systematic unaliving of journalists in full esteem and Lebanon.
I haven't seen you call attention to the complicity of Democrats in the advancement of Republicans in doing whatever the F they want in this nation.
No, you're just the latest blackface being used to continue the psychological operations that are lying to everybody.
And now you are not only lying to everybody, but you're continuing to lie to yourself.
You are nothing more than a narrative reader, which is why you are sitting here spewing the narrative that the United States government, the literal imperial death star of the world, has scripted you to say.
And so when you sit up here and you try to gaslight an entire nation that what took place was not a hoax, simply because you are not ready to wake up to the lie that you're living in, you're embarrassing yourself.
You don't even deserve to wear that natural.